Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- Milwaukee County Labor Council, Publication (Box 461, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Record of proceedings, 1962; Publication (Box 461, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan-Mar, Apr-July, Aug-Dec (1962)
  - Item 7: The decline of the daily press in public esteem, Publication (Box 461, Folder 6)
    Author: R. W. Talyor
    Notes: Based on a series of articles as originally appearing in the AFL-CIO Milwaukee Labor Press
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 461, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Record of proceedings, 1965; Publication (Box 461, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan, Mar-May, July-Dec (1965)
  - Item 2: Record of proceedings, 1966; Publication (Box 461, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan-May, July-Dec (1966)
  - Item 3: Record of proceedings, 1967; Publication (Box 461, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan-June, Aug-Dec (1967)
  - Item 4: Record of proceedings, 1968; Publication (Box 461, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan-Dec (1968)
  - Item 5: Record of proceedings, 1969; Publication (Box 461, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan-Sept (1969)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1959; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Record of proceedings, 1969; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Oct-Dec (1969)
  - Item 3: Record of proceedings, 1970; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan-Dec (1970)
  - Item 4: Record of proceedings, 1971; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan-Dec (1971)
  - Item 5: Record of proceedings, 1972; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan-Dec (1972)
  - Item 6: Record of proceedings, 1973; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan-June, Aug-Dec (1973)
  - Item 7: Record of proceedings, 1974; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan-Dec (1974)
  - Item 8: Record of proceedings, 1975; Publication (Box 461, Folder 8)
    Notes: Feb-Dec (1975)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Project Rehab/Newsletter. Respiratory diseases number "2" disabler in the nation, 1966; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Author: New York City Central Labor Council
    Notes: July 1, 1966.
  - Item 2: Project Rehab/Newsletter. Fact sheet on mental retardation, 1965; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Notes: Dec. 29, 1965.
  - Item 3: Project Rehab/Newsletter., 1963-1964 (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.1-7 (1963-1964)
  - Item 4: Project Rehab/Newsletter., 1967; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Notes: Mar. 7, 1967.
  - Item 5: UPP! Union purchasing plan., Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Have you registered??? Community Services Committee, 1968; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Labor and the intelligentsia, 1961; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Author: Harry Van Arsdale
  - Item 8: Outline of principles and programs labor rehabilitation liaison project of the New York City Central Labor Council, Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Labor Rehabilitation Liaison Project is pleased to announce a new addition to its program on behalf of the affiliates of the New York City Central Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Industrial Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Notes: Sept. 1966.
  - Item 11: The Union Leader as a decision maker, 1961; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
    Notes: Seminar flyer
  - Item 12: Commitment to education, Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Constitution and by-laws, 1959; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Announcing a practical workshop conference on how to use labor education in you union (flyer), 1964; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Unions meet automation and a program for action, 1960; Publication (Box 462, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 462, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1964; Publication (Box 462, Folder 2)
    Author: Niagara County Council
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 462, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Compare the records of GOP and Democratic rule, Publication (Box 462, Folder 3)
    Author: Philadelphia AFL-CIO
    Notes: Newspapers articles put out by Labor's League for Political Education
- Rochester History, Publication (Box 462, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Rochester History., 1963; Publication (Box 462, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.25:no.1 (1963)
- San Francisco Labor Council, Publication (Box 462, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Directory., 1965; Publication (Box 462, Folder 5)
    Author: San Francisco Labor Council
    Notes: Aug. 1, 1965.
  - Item 2: Directory., 1966; Publication (Box 462, Folder 5)
    Notes: July 1966.
  - Item 3: The San Francisco story, 1960; Publication (Box 462, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Automation: blessing or curse?. by Leon H. Keyserling, 1964; Publication (Box 462, Folder 5)
- San Francisco Labor Council, Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Meeting minutes., 1958; Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
    Notes: Nov-Dec (1958)
  - Item 2: Meeting minutes., 1959; Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.-Nov. (1959)
  - Item 3: Meeting minutes., 1960; Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb.-Apr., June-July, Sept., Nov.-Dec. (1960)
  - Item 4: Official Bulletin., 1958; Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
    Notes: no. 23-26, 28-32 (1958)
  - Item 5: Official Bulletin., 1959; Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.10:no.1-26 (1959)
  - Item 6: Official Bulletin., 1960; Publication (Box 463, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.11:no.1-9, 11-17, 19-27 (1960)
- San Francisco Labor Council, Publication (Box 463, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Meeting minutes., 1961; Publication (Box 463, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. (1961)
  - Item 2: Meeting minutes., 1962; Publication (Box 463, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. (1962)
  - Item 3: Official Bulletin., 1961; Publication (Box 463, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.12:no.1-17 (1961)
  - Item 4: Official Bulletin., 1962; Publication (Box 463, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.1-5, 7-17 (1962)
- San Francisco Labor Council, Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Official Bulletin., 1960; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.10 (1960)
  - Item 2: Official Bulletin., 1961; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.5, 13 (1961)
  - Item 3: Official Bulletin., 1963; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.1-21 (1963)
  - Item 4: Official Bulletin., 1964; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.15:no.1-3, 5-19 (1964)
  - Item 5: Meeting minutes., 1961; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan (1961)
  - Item 6: Meeting minutes., 1963; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan, Mar-Aug, Oct.-Nov. (1963)
  - Item 7: Meeting minutes., 1964; Publication (Box 463, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan, Mar-June, Oct.-Dec. (1964)
- San Francisco Labor Council, Publication (Box 463, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Official Bulletin., 1969; Publication (Box 463, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.20:no.6 (1969)
  - Item 2: Meeting minutes., 1969; Publication (Box 463, Folder 4)
    Notes: Aug. (1969)
  - Item 3: Meeting minutes., 1971; Publication (Box 463, Folder 4)
    Notes: July (1971)
- Steuben county Trades and Labor Council, Publication (Box 463, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Steuben Livingston Labor Report., 1958; Publication (Box 463, Folder 5)
    Author: Steuben county Trades and Labor Council
    Notes: July, Dec. (1958); v.1:no.2, 6 (1958)
  - Item 2: Steuben Livingston Labor Report., 1959; Publication (Box 463, Folder 5)
    Notes: Dec (1959)
  - Item 3: Steuben Livingston Labor Report., 1960; Publication (Box 463, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb., April (1960)
  - Item 4: IUE News CIO, Local 313., 1960; Publication (Box 463, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb.-Mar. (1960)
- Industrial Bulletin, Publication (Box 463, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Meet 'Young Hogan' (Industrial Bulletin, Dec. 1964); Syracuse mission's mission accoumplished (Industrial Bulletin, Feb. 1966), 1964-1966 (Box 463, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 463, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Conference folder, 1982; Publication (Box 463, Folder 7)
    Author: Metropolitan Washington Council AFL-CIO
  - Item 2: Unions and democracy, Publication (Box 463, Folder 7)
    Author: Benjamin D. Segal
    Notes: A brief account of problems in Union Democracy in The American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. c.2
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, Publication (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Progress Report, 1962-1980 (Box 464, Folder 1)
    Author: American Institute for Free Labor Development
  - Item 2: A union to union program for the Americas, 1979; Publication (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: V Western Hemisphere Labor Economics Conference, ORIT/AFL- CIO/AIFLD, 1979; Publication (Box 464, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th conference. Trade union rights and economic development, Washington, D.C., November 13-14, 1979. 2 copy
  - Item 4: Latin American labor and structural adjustments in the 90s, 1991; Publication (Box 464, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The American Federationist, 1983; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: The American Federationist
    Notes: v.90:no.1-5 (1983)
  - Item 2: The American Federationist, 1984; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.91:no.1, 4 (1984)
  - Item 3: The American Federationist, 1985; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.92:no.1, 5-7 (1985)
  - Item 4: The American Federationist, 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.93:no.7 (1986)
  - Item 5: The American Federationist, 1987; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.94:no.5 (1987)
  - Item 6: Work and family: essentials of a decent life: who is really "pro family.", 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Women at work: meeting the challenge of job and family, 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Carolyn J. Jacobson
  - Item 8: Unemployment still a key issue, 1984; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Markley Roberts
  - Item 9: America's foreign trade crisis, 1984; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Mark Anderson
  - Item 10: Productivity: policies and problems, 1984; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Bill Cunningham
  - Item 11: A question of fairness: the new attack on workers' life-support benefits, 1985; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Arnold Cantor
  - Item 12: Bargaining trends: gains in 1984, prospects for 1985, Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Neil Gladstein
  - Item 13: Workers without jobs, 1985; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: The tax reform that went wrong, 1985; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: A labor agenda for housing, 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Frank Parente
  - Item 16: Breaking new ground: bargaining in 1986, Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Jacqueline Simon
  - Item 17: The American Federationist, 1982; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.89 :no.5-7 (1982
  - Item 18: Jobs and freedom: still a long way to go for America's black workers, black families, 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Richard Womack; Markley Roberts
  - Item 19: It's time to raise the minimum wage, 1987; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Jay Mazur
  - Item 20: Roots of the trade crisis, 1987; Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Bargaining in 1987: against the wind, Publication (Box 464, Folder 2)
    Author: Matt Kane
- James Trenz, Publication (Box 464, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Mission to Africa, 1978; Publication (Box 464, Folder 3)
    Author: James Trenz
- Rudolph A. Oswald, Publication (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Statement by to the Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources on unemployment effects and remedies, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Statement byto the Senate Appropriations Committee, on the budget and the economy, 1981; Publication (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: StatementBefore the Subcommittee on Trade of the House of Representatives on the President's Report to the Congress on the First Five Years operation of the U.S. generalized system of preferences, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: StatementBefore the U.S. House Committee on Ways and Means on tax cut legislation, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Statementto the Subcommitteeon commerce, Consumer, and Monetary Affairs of the Committee on Government Operations of the House of Representatives on the Administration's Anti-inflation Program, 1979; Publication (Box 464, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: StatementBefore the Finance Committee, United States Senate on Hearings to Explore Advisability of Enactment of Tax Cuts, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
    Author: Lane Kirkland
  - Item 2: StatementBefore the Economic Stabilization Subcommittee of the Committee on Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, U.S. House of Representatives on the Industrial Competitiveness Act, H.R. 4360, and Related Acts, 1983; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: AFL-CIO News. Transcript of: Pres. Lane Kirkland's Press Conference., 1983; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb. 21, 1983. 2 copy
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO News. Transcript of Pres. Lane Kirklands News Conference at the Executive Council Meeting, 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb. 17, 1986.
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO News. Lane Kirkland EC Press Conference, 1989; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 2, 1989.
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO News. Transcript of Press Conference of Pres. Lane Kirkland., 1989; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
    Notes: Aug. 8, 1989.
  - Item 7: Toward a new foreign policy, 1989; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Solidarity...: key to the future, 1981; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: A foreign policy with a purpose, 1982; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Public school and the common good, 1982; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Constructive use of government, 1982; Publication (Box 464, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Statement of Before the Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures of the Committee on Ways & Means, US House of Representatives on the issue of repealing the 30-percent withholding tax on interest paid to foreign portfolio investors, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Stephen Koplan
  - Item 2: Statement of Before the Joint Economic Committee on 'Public Works as a countercyclical tool', 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Before the Committee on Labor and Human Resources, United States Senate, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Ray Denison
  - Item 4: Submitted Statement by the Before the Subcommittee on Antitrust, Monopoly and business rights Senate Judiciary Committee, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Statement by Before the House Government Operations Committee on extension of the revenue sharing act of 1972, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Statement of Before the Subcommittee on Monopolies and Commercial Law of the House Judiciary Committee on Constitutional Amendments to mandate a balanced Federal budget, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Laurence Gold
  - Item 7: Statement by To the House Subcommittee on Employment Opportunities on the Employment effects of current and proposed economic policies, fiscal 1981 budget cuts, Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Kenneth Young
  - Item 8: Statement of Before the Subcommittee on Labor Standards of the Committee on Education and Labor on the National Workers Compensation Standards Act of 1979, Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Barrett K. Seeley
  - Item 9: AFL-CIO Statement on controls, 1978; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Statement of before the Subcommittee on Financial Institutions Supervision, Regulation and Insurance of the House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs on the Home Mortgage Disclosure Act Amendments of 1980, Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Henry B. Schechter
  - Item 11: Summary of proceedings. Perspectives on labor research: a symposium for University and Union Researchers.sponsored by Cornell Univ. New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Div. of Extension and Public Service, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Statement by on the National Economy, 1986; Publication (Box 464, Folder 6)
    Author: Executive Council.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Solzhenitsyn, the voice of freedom, 1975; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
    Author: Aleksandr Isaevich Solzhenitsyn
    Notes: Two addresses. c.2
  - Item 2: Statement of before the Subcommittee on Consumer Affairs of the House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs on the Cash Discount Act and Fair Credit Practices Act, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Statement of Before the Subcommittee on Trade, Committee on Ways and Means U.S. House of Representatives Hearings on the Administration's Oil Import Fee, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Statement of Before the Committee on Ways and Means U.S. House of Representatives on the President's proposal for withholding on interest and dividends, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Statement by Before the Joint Hearings on Technology and Trade in the House of Representatives by the Committees on Science and Technology, Interstate, and Foreign Commerce, Finance and Urban Affairs, and the Task Force on Industrial Innovation, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Statement of Before the Committee on Foreign Relations of the U.S. Senate, on S. 2186, a bill to expand the lending and financing arrangements of the overseas private investment corporation, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Statement by Before the Senate Rules and Administration Committee on 'Sunset'. S. 2, 1980; Publication (Box 464, Folder 7)
    Author: Howard Marlowe
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: On this Labor Day 1980, Union members should consider how much organized labor has done for all workers, Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
    Author: Building and Construction Trades Dept.
  - Item 2: National Legislative Conference of the Building, 1981; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: National Conference of Building.to develop action program against legislative anti-labor forces, Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Building Trades President endorses pension fund exemption to increase investment in housing market, 1980; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: U.S. Chamber of Commerce is using Davis-Bacon repeal as camouflage in attack on free enterprise, 1980; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Georgine announces that political and economic problems will be high on agenda in Los Angeles at convention of Building and., Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Georgine endorses Congressional action on breeder reactor funds, Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Real motive of opponents of Situs Picketing Legislation is to destroy the trade union movement, 1977; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Georgine hails introduction of on-site picketing billsays it wil stabilize U.S. economy and restore workers' rights, 1977; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Workers should insist on knowing who really is behind advocacy efforts, Georgine urges in Labor Day message, 1977; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Georgine charges opponents to Situs Picketing Bill are motivated primarily by chance to destroy labor, 1977; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Public opinion poll shows support of equal treatment by almost two-to-one, 1977; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Voting records of members of 94th Congress on issues of importance to Building, distributed by thousands throughout nation, 1976; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: AFL-CIO Buildingprepares 'profile' of construction industry as basis for discussions at National Conference in Washington, 1976; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Remarks of Robert A. Georgine Before the 44th Convention of the Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Assoc. of the Unter States and Canada, 1979; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Construction Industry unemployment worsens, Building Trades' survey of 51 area shows, 1976; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: High interest rates and budget cuts are not solution to inflation, Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Windfall profits tax needed to prevent big oil rip-off, declares Building, Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Embargo! Embargo!, Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Statement by Bob Georgine, 1981; Publication (Box 465, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 465, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Plan for the settlement of jurisdictional disputes in the construction industry including procedural rules and regulations, 1993; Publication (Box 465, Folder 2)
    Notes: Approved by the Building and Construction Trades Department, ALF-CIO. 2 copy
  - Item 2: Plan for the settlement of jurisdictional disputes in the construction industry including procedural rules and regulations, 1990; Publication (Box 465, Folder 2)
    Notes: Approved by the Building and Construction Trades Department, ALF-CIO.
  - Item 3: Plan for the settlement of jurisdictional disputes in the construction industry, 1984; Publication (Box 465, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Procedural rules and regulations for the plan for the settlement of jurisdictional disputes in the construction industry, 1984; Publication (Box 465, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 465, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Plan for the settlement of jurisdictional disputes in the construction industry including procedural rules and regulations (photocopy), 1990; Publication (Box 465, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 465, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution and bylaws to govern local councils of the Building., 1985; Publication (Box 465, Folder 4)
    Notes: Amended Aug. 1985
  - Item 2: Constitution and bylaws to govern local councils of the Building., 1990; Publication (Box 465, Folder 4)
    Notes: Amended Nov. 1990
  - Item 3: Constitution and bylaws to govern local councils of the Building., 1993; Publication (Box 465, Folder 4)
    Notes: Reprinted March 1993
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 465, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Three Mile Island Recovery Project Agreement between Metropolitan Edison Company, Signatory Contractors and Building and Construction Trades Department, AFL-CIO and Signatory National and International Unions, 1980; Publication (Box 465, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Craft work rules and regulations. Three Mile Island Recovery Project Agreement, 1980; Publication (Box 465, Folder 5)